Narrator: 1
Version a
Speaker 1: ÔMr Watson,Ő she said slowly, ÔI am beginning to understand.Ő
Narrator: Version b
Narrator: 2
Version a
Speaker 2: ÔSit down,Ő he said calmly, Ôand tell me what you know.Ő
Narrator: Version b
Narrator: 3
Version a
Speaker 1: ÔCatherine,Ő he said nervously.
ÔThereŐs something I have to tell you.Ő
Narrator: Version b
Speaker 1: ÔCatherine,Ő he said nervously.
ÔThereŐs something I have to tell you.Ő
Narrator: 4
Version a
Speaker 2: ÔHere you are,Ő the old woman said kindly.
ÔA nice cup of tea for you.Ő
Narrator: Version b
Speaker 2: ÔHere you are,Ő the old woman said kindly.
ÔA nice cup of tea for you.Ő
Narrator: 5
Version a
Speaker 1: The detective looked at her suspiciously.
ÔTell me, what were you doing at 12.00 on 11th of May?Ő
Narrator: Version b
Speaker 1: The detective looked at her suspiciously.
ÔTell me, what were you doing at 12.00 on 11th of May?Ő